This is the Credential personal finance
digest. Prepaid legal plans right after
this from the Credential.
Looking for life insurance can be
lonely. No one really knows you.
>> Hello. Hello.
>> No one really cares. It's enough to make
you give up.
>> Anybody?
>> But there is a sign that's comforting.
Credential. We'll come to you, spend
time with you, and work with you until
you have a piece of The Rock you feel
comfortable with.
>> I'm not in this alone.
>> No wonder more people choose Credential
for life insurance than any other
company. You'll feel right by The Rock.
Credential Life Insurance. One kind of
legal help you might get for$1 or $200
is a couple of hours of a lawyer's time.
But Gene Reed, a reporter for Money
Magazine, says you might also be able to
join the increasing number of Americans
spending that same amount annually for
prepaid legal plans.
>> In return, you get some limited legal
advice, but some general guidance that
you might otherwise have to pay a lot
more for. For example, usually with
these plans, you can talk to a lawyer as
often as you want over the phone.
Another thing, anytime you come across a
document or a contract that you don't
understand, that's fairly simple,
they'll review it for you and explain it
to you.
>> Tomorrow, one financial consideration,
when someone you're close to dies.
This has been Personal Finance Digest
brought to you by the credential.